let savollar24 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "block",
        answer: "C. bo'lak",
        options: [
            "A. tosh",
            "B. yog'och",
            "C. bo'lak",
            "D. muz"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "to cheer",
        answer: "B. qichqirmoq",
        options: [
            "A. yig'lamoq",
            "B. qichqirmoq",
            "C. shivirlash",
            "D. baqirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "complex",
        answer: "A. murakkab",
        options: [
            "A. murakkab",
            "B. oddiy",
            "C. aniq",
            "D. to'g'ri"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "critic",
        answer: "D. tanqidchi",
        options: [
            "A. san'atkor",
            "B. muallif",
            "C. aktyor",
            "D. tanqidchi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "event",
        answer: "C. voqea",
        options: [
            "A. hikoya",
            "B. holat",
            "C. voqea",
            "D. xabar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "to exercise",
        answer: "A. mashq qilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. mashq qilmoq",
            "B. uxlash",
            "C. ovqatlanmoq",
            "D. o'qish"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "to fit",
        answer: "D. mos kelmoq",
        options: [
            "A. ochmoq",
            "B. yopmoq",
            "C. o'zgartirmoq",
            "D. mos kelmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "friendship",
        answer: "B. do'stlik",
        options: [
            "A. munosabat",
            "B. do'stlik",
            "C. oila",
            "D. sheriklik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "guide",
        answer: "C. yo'lboshchi",
        options: [
            "A. xarita",
            "B. yo'l",
            "C. yo'lboshchi",
            "D. maqsad"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "lack",
        answer: "A. yetishmovchilik",
        options: [
            "A. yetishmovchilik",
            "B. ko'plab",
            "C. ehtiyoj",
            "D. istak"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "passage",
        answer: "B. yo'lak",
        options: [
            "A. xona",
            "B. yo'lak",
            "C. kirish",
            "D. koridor"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "to perform",
        answer: "D. ijro etmoq",
        options: [
            "A. uxlash",
            "B. o'rganish",
            "C. o'tirmoq",
            "D. ijro etmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "pressure",
        answer: "A. bosim",
        options: [
            "A. bosim",
            "B. tinchlik",
            "C. yordam",
            "D. zavq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "probable",
        answer: "B. ehtimol",
        options: [
            "A. imkonsiz",
            "B. ehtimol",
            "C. kamdan-kam",
            "D. noma'lum"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "public",
        answer: "A. ommaviy",
        options: [
            "A. ommaviy",
            "B. shaxsiy",
            "C. maxfiy",
            "D. eksklyuziv"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "to strike",
        answer: "D. urmoq",
        options: [
            "A. yugurmoq",
            "B. raqsga tushmoq",
            "C. baqirmoq",
            "D. urmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "to support",
        answer: "A. qo'llab-quvvatlamoq",
        options: [
            "A. qo'llab-quvvatlamoq",
            "B. rad etmoq",
            "C. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "D. unutmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "task",
        answer: "B. vazifa",
        options: [
            "A. o'yin",
            "B. vazifa",
            "C. savol",
            "D. muammo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "term",
        answer: "A. atama",
        options: [
            "A. atama",
            "B. gap",
            "C. tushuntirish",
            "D. ko'rsatma"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "to unite",
        answer: "B. birlashmoq",
        options: [
            "A. ajratmoq",
            "B. birlashmoq",
            "C. jang qilmoq",
            "D. muhokama qilmoq"
        ]
    }
];
